Edward Livingston Papers, 1683-1877 (bulk 1764-1836 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 1: Edward Livingston (1764-1836), 1781-1877; 1781-1836; 94 boxes
  - Subseries 1A: Correspondence, 1784-1836; 56 boxes
    - General, 1784-1836; 45 boxes
      - Jones, William D., 1829-1835; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Joy, G., 1834; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Judah, Benjamin S., 1795; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Juget, 1812; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Julius, M., 1834-1836; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Jumonville, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - J: Unidentified, 1805; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Kane, E.K., 1794-1835, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Kearny, Philip, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Keene, Luther Martin, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Keene, Richard Raynal, 1805-1811; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Keene, Richard Raynal, 1824-1832; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Kelly, M., 1830; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Kelly, Thomas, 1820; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Kelly, William, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Kemper, Daniel, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Kemper, Jacob, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Kemper, Reuben, 1812-1824; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Kendall, Amos, 1789-1869, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Kennedy, Isaac, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Kennedy, John G., 1801; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Kennedy, Thomas S., 1811; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Kenne, William, 1813; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Kent, James, 1763-1847, 1787-1814; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Ker, H. Bellenden, 1831-1834; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Kerr, John Leeds, 1780-1844, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Kerr, Louis, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Ketchum, Micah, 1791; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Keteltas, William, 1801-1803; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Key, Francis Scott, 1779-1843, 1820-1835; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Key, Philip B., 1757-1815, 1809-1815; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Kilshaw and Co., 1829-1830; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - King, John A., 1788-1867, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - King, S., 1802; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - King, William R. D., 1786-1853, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Kingsland, J.S., 1820; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Kingston, Stephen, 1793-1801; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Kip, I., Jr., 1800; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Kip, Isaac L., 1820-1824; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Kirkland, R.B., 1823-1825; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Knapp, Samuel L., 1783-1838, 1827-1833; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Knox, George, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Kuhn, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - K: Unidentified, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - L'Enfant, Piere Charles, 1754-1825, 1801; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - L'Espinasse, L'Abbe de, 1811-1833; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - La Branche, Louis, 1823; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - La Croix, Du Suan, 1824-1836; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - La Grange, J.M. de, 1830-1835; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - La Hogue, J.B.M. de, 1804; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - La Ronde, Denis, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - La Rousse, Rey, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Labatte, J.B., 1813-1814; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Labernard, Duboys, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Labrouche, Jaques, undated; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Lacroix, Paul, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Ladd, William, 1778-1841, 1826-1832; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Lafayette, George Washington, 1779-1849, 1796-1835; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Lafayette, Marie A.F. de Noailles, Marquise, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Lafayette, Marquis de, 1757-1834, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Lafayette, Marquis de, 1757-1834, 1818-1819; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Lafayette, Marquis de, 1757-1834, 1821; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Lafayette, Marquis de, 1757-1834, 1822-1825; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Lafayette, Marquis de, 1757-1834, 1827-1829; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Lafayette, Marquis de, 1757-1834, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Lafayette, Marquis de, 1757-1834, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Lafayette, Marquis de, 1757-1834, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Lafayette, Marquis de, 1757-1834, 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Lafayette, Marquis de, 1757-1834, 1824-1956; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Laffite, Pierre, 1814; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Lafon, 1810; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Lafontaine, P.D. Cailleau, 1812-1814; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Lakanal, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Lallemand, Charles, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Lamarlere, A. (and wife), 1809-1831; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Lamb, Anthony, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Lamb, John, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Lambert, John, 1815; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Lambert, P., 1824; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Lameson, 1815; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Lamotte, J., 1812; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Lanaux, Charles, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Lancaster, Joseph, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Langdon, John, 1796-1803; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Lanna, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Lansing, John, Jr., 1754-1829, 1784-1801; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Lansingh, Jerimiah, 1789-1793; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Lanthoise, John, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Lanusse, Paul, 1810-1824; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Larrabie, Charles, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Latel, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Latham, James, 1785-1786; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Latham, Richard, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Latour, A., 1813; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Latour, Arsene Lecarrier, 1808-1816; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Latour, Arsene Lecarrier, 1818-1835; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Latour, Charles de, 1806-1807; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Latrobe, Benjamin Henry, 1764-1820, 1812-1814; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Latrobe, undated; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Laughlin, John, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Laurance, John, 1750-1810, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Lauret, Louis, 1824-1829; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Laussat, Anthony, 1806-1833, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Lauve, Nicholas, 1824-1826; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Lavergne, H., 1827; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Laverty, Kenny, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Law, Thomas, 1759-1834, 1802-1803; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Lawler, Mathew, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Lawrence, Aaron, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Lawrence, Cornelius W., 1834; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Lawrence, Julia, 1836; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Lawrence, William, 1814; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Le Blanc, Joseph, 1811; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Le Blanc, T., 1823-1826; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Le Breton Dorengo, P.J., 1812; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Le Carpentier, Joseph, 1824-1833; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Le Doux, 1795-1796; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Le Fort, 1812; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Le Guen, L., 1798; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Le Marchant, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Le Monnier, Yves, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Leaumont, Nicolas-Marie, Vicomte de, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Ledyard, Isaac, 1801-1802; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Ledyard, Susan, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Lee, Arthur, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Lee, C.C., 1829-1831; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Lee, Edmund J., 1830; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Lee, Gideon, 1778-1841, 1833-1834; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Lee, H., 1756-1818, 1815; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Lee, Henry, 1821-1834; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Lee H., 1787-1837, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Lee, Richard Henry, 1794-1865, undated; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Lee, William, 1815-1823; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Leeuwarden, M.J., 1833; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Lefebvre, Modeste, 1809-1828; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Legare, Hugh Swinton, 1797-1843, 1831-1836; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Lelouef, J., 1833; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Lent, Abraham, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Leonard, John, 1830-1833; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Lerebourg, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Lestaf, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Letcher, Robert P., 1833-1835; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Lewis, E., 1813-1830; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Lewis, Thomas C., 1818-1819; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Lewis, William, 1751-1819, 1793-1801; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Lewis, William B., 1784-1866, 1828-1834; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Liais, Eugene, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Liancourt, Duc de, 1799; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Liddle, William, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Lieber, Francis, 1800-1872, 1828-1835; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Lillers, E. de, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Lincoln, Levi, 1749-1820, 1801; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Lincoln, Levi, 1782-1868, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Lindsley, A.B., 1829; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Lindsley, Philip, 1786-1855, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Linton, John, 1827; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Lippitt, J. Francis, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Liquet, 1812; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - List, Georg Friedrich, 1789-1846, 1830-1834; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Liston, Robert, 1742-1836, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Livermore, Samuel, 1786-1833, 1824-1825; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Livingstone, Edward, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Lockett, Henry, 1831-1836; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Lockett, Winfrey, 1817; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Loere-Veimars, A., undated; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Lompre, Claude S. de, 1812-1813; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Longacre, James B., 1834; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Longpre, J., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Longuerac, Dufour, 1817-1818; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Longworth, David, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Lonsdale, J., 1834; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Lorillard, Peter, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Loring, Israel, 1795-1796; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Loss, Charles, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Lossing, Peter, 1790-1803; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Lot, Jean Marie d', 1815; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Lott, Abraham, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Lott, Johannis E., 1798; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Louaillier, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 58)
      - Loudon, Sam, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 59)
      - Louis Philippe, King of France, 1773-1850, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 60)
      - Louvet, Edouard, 1826-1831; 1 folder (Folder 61)
      - Lovell, Joseph, 1788-1836, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 62)
      - Lovett, John, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 63)
      - Low, Jacobus, 1787; 1 folder (Folder 64)
      - Low, Nicholas, 1739-1826, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Lowndes, Thomas, 1831-1836; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Lowrey, Thomas, 1790-1791; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Lowrie, Walter, 1784-1868, 1818; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Lozano, Joaquin, 1808; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Ludeling, J. Henry, 1813-1817; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Ludlow, Daniel, 1750-1814, Robert, C., Jr., and Ludlow, Daniel, Jr., 1796-1825; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Ludlow, William H., 1788-1791; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Ludlow and Gould, 1787; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Lyle, Henry, 1795-1800; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Lyman, Thomas, 1799; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Lynch, Charles, 1804-1806; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Lynch, Francis, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Lynch, Jasper, 1828-1829; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Lynch, Nicholas, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Lynch, undated; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Lynd, Henriette, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Lynd, John, 1816; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Lyon, George, 1798-1803; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Lyon, J., 1811-1812; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Lyte, Edward Jordan, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Lytle, William, 1814; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - L: Unidentified, 1788-1836; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Macarty, A.H., 1834; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Macarty, Benjamin, 1824-1831; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Macdonald, A., 1822-1823; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Macdonald, J., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Mackay, Aeneas, 1794; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Mackenzie, A., undated; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - MacKinnen, D., 1800; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Macomb, Alexander, 1748-1832, 1796-1799; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Macomb, Alexander, 1782-1841, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Macon, Nathaniel, 1758-1837, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Madier, de St. Andre, 1812; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Madison, James, 1751-1836, 1802-1835; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Madison, James, 1751-1836, 1801-1834; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Magenis, A.L., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Maison-Rouge, John, 1818-1819; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Malcolm, Howard, 1827; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Malenfant, J.R., 1817; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Malin, David and Sedgwick, Charles B., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Mallett, E.J., undated; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Mancius, Catherine, 1820; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Mancius, George W., 1796; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Mangin, 1794-1818, 1795-1798; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Manhattan Company, undated; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Marans, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - March, Samuel, 1801; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Marcorelle, A., 1795-1803; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Marcy, William L., 1786-1857, 1833-1834; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Marigny, Bernard, 1785-1868, 1805-1832; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Marsenat, 1808-1813; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Marsh, Silas and Marsh, Silas, Jr., 1788; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Marsh, William, 1800-1801; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Marshall, H., 1831-1832; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Martin, William D., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Masclet, 1796-1797; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Mason, J., 1823-1826; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Mason, Stevens Thomson, 1760-1803, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Masson, H.N., 1823; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Mather, George, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Mathews, J.M., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Maule, Thomas, 1797-1807; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Maxcy, Virgil, 1785-1844, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Maybin, Joseph A., 1824-1832; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Mayer, Charles F., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Mazureau, 1777-1849, 1805-1824; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - McAllister, John, 1825-1826; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - McCann, Charles, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - McCaleb, Thomas F., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 60)
      - McCarty, David, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - McClenahan, James J., 1824; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - McClintic, John, circa 1827; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - McClure, Richard, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - McCormick, Daniel and Arden, Jacob, 1804; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - McCutchon, Samuel W., 1820; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - McDavitt, Patrick, 1789; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - McDonald, Alexander, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - McDonogh, John, 1779-1850, 1824-1832; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - McEuen, Thomas, 1790-1798; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - McEvers, LeRoy, 1830-1835; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - McFarlane, J.S., 1829; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - McGinnes, B., 1824; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - McKean, J.B., 1764-1826, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - McKee, John, 1771-1832, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - McKinnen, Daniel, 1801-1805; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - McKinney, Mathew, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - McKinny, Arthur M., 1795; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - McLane, Louis, 1786-1857, 1829-1831; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - McLane, Louis, 1786-1857, 1832-1834; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - McLean, John, 1785-1861, 1826-1830; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - McMahon, J. de Coulant, 1827-1829; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - McMaster and Adams, 1812; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - McMicken, Charles, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - McNeal, William, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - McNeale, 1810; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - McQuhae, John G., 1820; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - McVicar, Archibald, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Mead, A.B., 1829; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Meade, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Mease, James, 1771-1846, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Mechanics' Bank, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Mechanics Society, 1802-1803; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Mendes, A., 1819; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Menon, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Mercein, Thomas R., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Mercier, J.J., 1826-1827; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Mercier, O., circa 1820; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Mericult, John F., 1805-1807; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Merry, A., 1805; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Merwin, John L., 1794; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Messonier, Henry, 1815; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Metcalfe, G., 1793; 1 folder (Folder 58)
      - Metcalfe, Henry, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 59)
      - Metoyer, Benjamin, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Meyer, J.D., 1834; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Meyer, John, 1795-1798; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Micali, Joseph, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Michel, Albin, 1810-1823; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Middleton, Henry, 1770-1846, 1831-1832; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Miles, James, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Milk, Benjamin, 1798-1807; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Millaudon, L., 1829-1836; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Miller, George, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Miller, Jacob, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Miller, John, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Miller, John, Jr., 1800; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Miller, Robert, 1824-1829; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Miller, Samuel, 1769-1850, 1801; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Miller, Sylvanus, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Miller, William, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Miller, 1820; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Mills, W.S., 1834; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Milnor, William, 1816; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Mincklar, Relian, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Minkler, Adam, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Mitchell, John, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Mitchell, Samuel L., 1803-1828; 1 folder (Folder 61)
      - Mitchell, Robert, 1830-1831; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Mix, Amos, 1793-1796; 1 folder (Folder 62)
      - Mogg, Christian, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Montfort, William G., 1801; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Monro, Milne and Co., 1824; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Monroe, James, 1758-1831, 1824-1829; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Montegut, Gabrielle, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Montegut, Pierre, 1815-1822; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Montegut, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Montgomery, George Washington, 1804-1841, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Montgomery, John B., 1794-1873, 1835-1836; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Montgomery, John C., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Montgomery, Robert, 1794; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Montgomery, W.W., 1810-1834; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Moore, Andrew, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Moore, Andrew, 1752-1821, 1791; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Moore, T.M., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 63)
      - Moore, T.P., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Morales, Antonio, 1807; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Morales, Juan Ventura de, 1804-1806; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Mordecai, A., 1829-1834; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - More, John, 1790-1796; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Moreau, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 64)
      - Moreau-Lislet, Louis, 1817-1831; 1 folder (Folder 44)
        Some letters relate to Felix Armand.
      - Morgan, Benjamin, 1806-1812; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Morgan, Benjamin R., 1800; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Morgan, David B., 1820-1830; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Morgan, G.W., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Morgan, John, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Morgan, Mary and Foley, Eliza, 1808; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Morgan, Patrick, 1805; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Morhouse, A., 1806; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Morhouse, Charles F., 1829-1830; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Morin, undated; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Morphy, Drego, 1814; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Morris, Easten, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Morris, Robert, Jr., 1799; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Morris, Staats, 1821; 1 folder (Folder 58)
      - Morris, Thomas, 1819; 1 folder (Folder 59)
      - Morris, William W., 1791-1798; 1 folder (Folder 60)
      - Morse, Nathan, 1828-1832; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Morton, Jacob, 1795-1835; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Morton, John A., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Morton, Washington Q., 1833; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        Includes case information for Peyroux and Al. Claimants of Steamboat Planter v. Howard and Varrion, 1833
      - Mouchon, Jean, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Moulder, John N., 1830; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Mouler, 1799; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Mouton, A., 1829; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Mullowny, John F., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Mumford, Gurdon S., 1764-1831, 1798-1829; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Mumford, William C., 1805; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Munro, Peter Jay, 1767-1833, 1795-1797; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Murat, Achille, 1801-1847, 1828-1834; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Murray, G.W., 1823-1824; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Muse, James Fort, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Musson, G., 1835; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - M: Unidentified, 1808-1818; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Nadaud, Jaques, 1819; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Nancarrow, John, 1808-1824; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Nathan, Simon, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Negrier, R.E., undated; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Neilson, William, 1795-1812; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Nesbitt, John, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - New York, Corporation of the City of, circa 1820; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - New York Historical Society, 1817; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - New York University, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Newton, Charles, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Nicholas, John, 1756-1819, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Nicholas, P.N., 1775-1849, 1824-1832; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Nicholas, Robert Carter, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Nicholas, Edward C., 1805; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Nichols, Arthur St. Clair, 1827-1828; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Nichols, Austin, 1799-1803; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Nicholson, John, 1822-1823; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Nicolas, Joseph, 1826-1835; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Niles, N., 1791-1869, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Nisbet, Alexander, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Noble, Arthur, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Noble, Thomas, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Nolte, V., 1779-1852, undated; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - North, William, 1755-1836, 1827-1831; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Norwood, Andrew and Others, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Nott, William, 1824-1827; 1 folder (Folder 59)
      - Nourse, Jjoseph, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Nuton, Charles, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - O'Duhigg, 1805-1806; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - O'Sullivan-Bear, B., 1828; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Oakford, Richard, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Oakley, Thomas J., 1783-1857, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Obregon, P., 1825-1827; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Obrie, N., 1836; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Obryan, John, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Oellers, James, 1801; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Ogden, David A., 1791; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Ogden, David B., 1775-1849, 1822-1834; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Ogden, Francis B., 1783-1857, 1814-1832; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Ogden, Peter V., 1812; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Ogden, Robert, 1826-1829; 1 folder (Folder 57)